everybody you are back
it is jack murphy this is the jack
murphy live podcast you can find me
on twitter at jack murphy live the
website jackmurphylive.com
the book is democrat to deplorable it is
available on amazon
and my men's group is called the liminal
order and our three core values are
brotherhood
masculinity and sovereignty if that
interests you come down check us out at
liminalhyphenorder.com but today we have
a guest that i've been wanting to have
on for quite some time
his name is kyle scheidler he is the
director for homeland security and
counterterrorism
at the center for security policy and he
is
an expert on antifa kyle how are you
welcome to the jack murphy live podcast
it's great to be here jack i appreciate
it
yeah it's absolutely my pleasure i saw
your testimony in front of congress i
read all that
watched the video and realized this was
a guy that i had to talk to
uh not to mention you're also yet
another member of the claremont network
i seem to be having a number of those
guys on doing great work out there
as always ryan williams and team at
claremont
and so antifa antifa is something that
we've been hearing about a ton
in the news lately for people who are
sort of just coming to understand them
it can be kind of
a confusing thing to understand what
antifa is especially when we hear
our politicians saying things like
antifa
is just an idea not an organization
which i
laugh at because i personally have
experience with antifa
antifa as an organized domestic terror
organization in my opinion
a few years ago they decided that i was
supposed to be canceled and so they
found me they doxed me
they contacted my employer they
contacted my little league board and
they did everything they could do to
ruin my life and this was done by a
woman
who was flying an antifa flag on the
banner of her twitter page who claimed
to be the head of the dc
unit of antifa and she clearly marshaled
forces of an organized online network to
come after me
and so when people say antifa is just an
idea i laugh
and we see everything that's been
happening all summer long
and so we need to get the word out and
we need to understand exactly what's
going on with antifa and that's why kyle
is here today so we're going to get
right into it
first thing i want to do is i want to
understand a little bit about you kyle
can you tell us a little bit about your
background how you came to this position
your expertise
just a little bit of your background
story so that the viewers can understand
who we're talking to here
uh sure so i guess my experience or
interest in these sort of
uh violent fringe political movements
really began in about
middle school where i decide when i
decided that i was an anarcho-communist
for a few years uh in about sixth grade
and i read uh bakunin and i read
kropopopkin and i moved on to lenin and
what is to be done uh you know so i'm
reading lenin's what is to be done
in uh in probably seventh grade
and i'm just totally fascinated by all
of this stuff
and i liken it to what i call uh
sort of the gi joe uh cobra syndrome
which is that the bad guys just had
cooler stuff
it was just cool uh you know
the the black leather car coat the
jaunty little cap the makarov
it's all cool and i want and i was
really interested in all of it and
fascinated in it
and i got interested in uh george orwell
uh reading his account of the spanish
civil war which had you know
the role of the the anarchists and their
suppression by the communists and
and all of this stuff was fascinating to
me and so i was always fascinated by
by uh revolutionary politics uh
but through reading orwell uh and some
other things i got into
um i started to realize actually there's
nothing
uh truly revolutionary about these
concepts at all
uh they never actually establish human
freedom
uh and then i started saying well what
what would
uh what would help establish human
freedom what would be a just system
and i got really into john locke
and the second treaty on government and
through them into the founders
and i decided that that actually the
american founders
uh had the best most truly revolutionary
uh understanding about how to establish
a just society on the basis of
of true equality of true political
equality and
i decided that was it i was going to be
uh i was going to be a defender of what
the founders believed
and i was going to work against uh all
of these
various uh revolutionary movements that
were trying to supplant that so i became
fascinated with that
uh i graduated from boston university
with a degree in politics and literature
and then i do what everybody does when
they graduate with a liberal arts degree
and i moved over my parents garage
and i was there for a while until i got
a job briefly
as a radio journalist in a small
town in north georgia it's actually the
same town where they film the movie
deliverance
okay and so i had all these grand ideas
and things i was interested in
and then during the day i was covering
county water sewer
meetings uh and so i started blogging
and writing and a group out in la became
interested in what i was doing and they
asked me to come on board and be a
researcher
uh and that group was called stand with
us and what they did was they were
tracking
extremist groups targeting jewish
students on college campuses
and so that's where i honed my my skills
actually digging into
digging into groups and organizations
and tracking individuals and
and determining what they believe and
why they believe it
uh eventually i made the jump to
washington dc
uh worked my way into the orbit of the
center for security policy
uh actually your prior guest dave reboy
and i actually went up for the same job
uh and he beat me out so he he joined
the center a little bit before i did
uh but i'm so i'm still there and still
doing the same stuff
um but this was you know this was during
the period of the war on terror and our
involvement in the middle east and so uh
as fascinated as i was with you know
violent leftist politics
uh it was islamism and the muslim
brotherhood and the jihadists that were
the topic du jour so i became very
focused on that
focused on the muslim brotherhood
movement the muslim brotherhood inside
the united states uh and trying to as
best i could
figure out how their ideology informs
their doctrine because what you believe
determines how you organize and it
determines how you operate
and so when people say
antifa is just an idea that's clearly
nonsense
but they do have an idea and if we
understand what the
idea is we can understand how it will
determine how they operate
and then we can try to defeat them
so you're an obviously expert on this
you're qualified to talk about it's been
a lifelong interest of yours you do this
professionally you've been in front of
congress to talk about these matters
you know what you're doing you know the
lay of the land so let's
start at the top antifa is very
important for all of us to understand
today
you can go outside on a random friday
night
in washington dc and encounter these
groups of people marching through the
city demanding
obedience setting fires even destroying
property assaulting police officers i've
seen it all happen
first hand and we get this report from
the politicians that say antifa is just
an idea okay well let's start with the
idea
and then work our way through the entire
thing because
i don't really think the general public
has any idea of what's going on with
antifa its history
its organization its structure how
they've evolved their tactics evolution
uh what their effectiveness is and what
the risk is that we face here in the
united states domestically
from a group that seems to have the only
goal in mind which is destroying the
power and the reach of the united states
government so
what is the idea and then
let's take it through their history and
their organization
and how they recruit etc let's drill
down deep i want people to understand so
let's start at the top
sure so i like to say um why don't we
start at the beginning in the beginning
is about
1932 with the founding of
anti-fascist action in weimar republic
germany
and it is founded as an arm of the
communist party of germany
which is itself uh controlled by
uh the stalin stalin and the comm intern
so let's clarify that for one second
right people think that communism and
fascism are like the same thing so how
can
how can these people be anti-communist
or communist or fascist like how does
that work if are communism and fascism
the same thing how are you against
fascism but still communists sure well
um so a lot of people like to say well
they're uh you know anti-fascism
but they're actually being fascist in
their behavior
and it's important to remember during
you know in wyoming republic
in fact almost every political party had
a militia
because if you didn't the other party
militia would come and shut you down
and in fact antifa despite the name
were not actually focused on fighting
the nazis they were actually focused on
fighting the social democrats
uh and fighting the center left and the
center right
because uh the the strategic
move was to force people to make a
choice
you are either going to be supporting
the communist or you're going to be
supporting the nazis
and their logic was well people are
going to reject the nazis and they'll
come on board with the communists
and that's how we'll win turns out they
were wrong about that
and so they end up getting suppressed
but that was the essential logic
and i like to start there because it's
the same logic today
antifa's goal is principally to force
you to make a choice
you are either pro-antifa meaning
literally you are pro-antifa you are
part of their movement
or you are a fascist choose this sounds
familiar right it sounds familiar like
either you're a racist
or you're not a racist what is it yeah
well
you know if you listen to the language
of like uh ibrahim kennedy right
it's you can't be not racist you can
only be racist or
anti-racist that's right anti-right if
you are not on board
with if their entire program you are a
racist in the same way that if you are
not on board with antifa you are a
fascist
and while they do fight you know the
occasional neo-nazi
group their real goal is to prevent
non-fascist groups
from organizing and participating in
politics
which they do very effectively by
branding them as fascists and then
normal mainstream people don't want to
have anything to do with them
because normal mainstream people aren't
fascists
uh and and uh and so then they
antifa rules the streets and there's no
political uh
opposition against them and so that's
the goal and so
it's it's an important thing to remember
that antifa operates with an
understanding of revolutionary politics
not everyday normal modern politics
where
my party wins one year your party wins
the next year
they are looking at it as a system where
the normal order has broken down
and so they can win uh with street
politics they can win with revolutionary
politics
which has this threat of force behind it
but so they are rep
they are suppressed uh and we don't
really hear about them
again until the 1980s so
like most of the western world in
germany in the
nineteen 1960s early nineteen seventies
uh germany is
rocked by a series of communist urban
guerrilla movements
uh for your listeners who have heard the
term the bottermeinhof gang
or red army faction in italy
you had the red brigades
and these are were communist urban
guerrilla movements that were
motivated in part by an ideology called
autonomism it's where we get the term
autonomous
it's it's where you get uh capitol hill
autonomous zone
right where they where they made that
decision to create that space
and so uh these guerrilla movements are
suppressed by the german government and
by the other european governments
and the ideology flows from them
into uh what was then the german
squatters rights movement
uh which was part of a larger sort of
punk uh gutter punk
rock scene and they form
a group called antifa and they proceed
to fight with german police
over their autonomous squats that
they've set up
and they took over in some cases because
this is germany you know post-war
you got a lot of abandoned buildings
whole blocks abandoned
right that they're slowly trying to
gentrify and reestablish
and the squatters move in and take these
things over and run them
according to their autonomous politics
and then street fight with the police
uh when the police try to break them up
it's where the term
uh black bloc for those of you who are
familiar with that term
it's where that originated was from the
um
the organization of fighting units
against uh of the german squatters
against the
against the german police
so it then jumps the pond to
london uh and again the punk rock scene
is where it's focused
uh and the punks are fighting with uh
skinheads and some uh some skinheads are
fighting against
uh right wing or what they perceive to
be fascist or neo-nazi skinheads
uh and they latch on to this concept of
uh
antifa and and work to push out
uh the right wing punks or the or the
neo-nazi punks from the
from the movement it jumps from there to
the united states
uh where you have a similar punk rock
scene uh but in the united states nobody
knows what a fascist is in the 1980s
or we're not really it doesn't mean
anything to us and so they use the name
anti-racist action instead of
anti-fascist action
but it's the same group uh same concept
and there they link up with the remnants
of america's communist urban gorilla
movement of the late 60s
and 70s a group which was known as the
may 19th communist organization
or better known by their front
organization the john brown anti-clan
committee
hold up for your readers will hold up a
book called no fascist usa which came
out a few years ago
and it is all about the john brown
anti-clan committee and
how it can inform today's antifa
movement
so the left understands this history
that i'm giving you
very well and i i derive this history
from their own
their own history this is what they say
happen so i i just take them at their
word
and so how does how does how does this
idea
survive then 30s and then sort of go
away for a while and then come back in
the 60s and then
migrate to england and then over to the
united states
you know how is the idea kept alive
how is the organization kept alive
you know is there literature is there
you know a canon
like how does this information survive
and get transmitted
absolutely well you know revolutionary
leftists better than anyone
study their own history so
you know as i was researching uh antifa
one of the things i did was go to
marxist.org
which has a great great repository of
revolutionary leftist writing
uh that's useful for studying
so on the one hand you have the fact
that leftists are just good at
understanding their own doctrine and
where they come from
and then of course you have the the also
you have the cold war influence
so the communist urban guerrilla
movements
uh in europe and the united states in
the late 60s early 70s
and into the early 80s did have ties to
uh various communist governments so in
the german example you've got ties to
the east german stasi
and in the u.s example you have ties
between the weather underground which
then becomes may 19th
communist organization and the cubans
and so uh there's an institutional
memory in
in that way as well uh weather
underground
is connected to may 19th and john brown
yes that's right so
uh the weather underground which is the
term probably your audience is pretty
familiar with
uh but they towards the
end of the 70s beginning of the 80s
there's a split in the movement
and the primarily the new york faction
an east coast faction goes on to found
something called the may 19th communist
organization
which decides to continue uh domestic
terrorism as a model
uh they link up with uh the black
liberation army
they link up with the puerto rican fln
uh f-a-l-n excuse me and they continue
to
to prosecute domestic terrorism in the
united states i think it's important to
point out for
in in the late 60s the weather
underground was responsible for i think
upwards of even like a thousand
bombings on college campuses in one year
is that right
i mean those late 60s were nuts for
domestic terrorism
that's right i mean you got the great
book days of rage that is worth reading
um on this you have the bombing in 1983
of the u.s senate office
you have the 1981 brinks armored car
robbery
very famous case um
and and so they were they were doing uh
they were doing domestic terrorism into
the late 80s or into the early
earth into the early 80s most people
don't know that but it's
it's true uh you have for example asada
shakur
uh for audiences familiar with asada
shakur she was a
leading member of the black liberation
army
she goes to jail for shooting a police
officer
the may 19th communist organization
breaks her out of jail
and helps her escape to cuba
and she's still in cuba today and is
still a martyr and mentor
of revolutionary leftist politics in the
united states
uh for example you have one of the
leaders of the black lives matter
movement who described asada shakur
as her mentor you have the the curious
fact
that blm's early fiscal sponsor is this
group called thousand currents
who's one of their board members was
susan rosenberg
a may 19th communist organization member
who
was pardoned by uh bill clinton for her
role in various uh criminal
uh bombings and other terrorist acts so
these
roots go deep and i i think it's really
important that we understand
that these roots go deep this is not a
new thing uh
revolutionary leftist violence is not a
new thing in the united states
uh by any stretch of the imagination we
just haven't seen it for a while
is there literature are there books are
there
you know handbooks like how do they
transmit this information
from generation to generation sure they
teach it
they quite literally teach it um in the
academy
where a number of weather underground
individuals went on
to work uh they fund it
through various by the academy you mean
universities that's right
yeah colleges and universities so they
teach it in the universities
uh and they uh they write books about it
they you know you mentioned the handbook
the antifa handbook was
written by prof uh now former professor
i think mark bray
uh which is it is literally a handbook
on how to be antifa i mean
when he says handbook he's not kidding
right uh so and he relates a lot of this
uh historical information about
uh you know the roots of this concept of
quote-unquote anti-fascism
and so i mean and it does so fairly
honestly i mean
um you know he does sort of say the goal
of antifa is to make it impossible to be
uh to be a trump supporter for example
you know and so if you're if you're
labeling you know 45
49 of the country fascist
we have to sort of question your
judgment right exactly so
there's been a tie through history
there's a message that's been
that was that was born in 1930s
in germany it has traveled the world it
has come to the united states it was
executed upon in the 60s and the 70s
into the 80s
even the literature lives on they're
educating people
in these ideas and tactics within the
universities they're producing handbooks
they're disseminating information
and so how does how does antifa evolve
from the 80s into what we're seeing
today
sure so you have the the anti-racist
action groups
uh one of their leaders um
the individual that runs anti-racist
action in los angeles
uh was a former member of the weather
underground and a former member of the
john brown anti-clan committee
and they transitioned into uh he
he is the uh website registrar for torch
antifa network
which is the largest regional network of
antifa in the country
and is the regional network network
which rose city antifa is a member of
rose city antifa being the oldest known
organization to go by antifa in the
united states
so you have a direct sort of lineal uh
connection between the early days of
anti-racist action
and the antifa of today as sort of the
in the
the leadership level they don't like the
term leadership because they're
anarchists
but they do have methods of decision
making and some people are in fact more
important than others
but you have you know you have a lot of
evolution of
thinking they are in a lot of ways
uh because they're anarchists and
because they're anarchist organized
uh they had a jump on a lot of the
fourth generation warfare
metric uh networked insurgency models
that we're only now thinking about
because of our fights
in the middle east with the various
jihadists but the
the anarchist model of organizing is was
way ahead
of all these guys in terms of doing that
and so
uh we should we should know better
fourth generation warfare something that
we've studied and talked about quite a
bit on this podcast we've got
john robb who is a regular contributor
he's coming back again to talk about
fourth generation warfare within the
liminal order fourth generation warfare
is a fundamental concept that we study
and we study it because the fourth
generation warfare
as it's being conducted today is not
necessarily tied to nation states it's
tied to ideas and to causes and even to
gangs
uh and it is a a conflict that has
no clearly set defined battlefield it
has no clear set
um you know participants you know you're
not wearing a uniform you don't have
identification as being a combatant
and it's all around us at all times and
and primarily today we're seeing it
through
well not just primarily anymore man it's
kind of sad but uh through
information warfare propaganda mind
control
bending perceptions changing notions of
reality
disinformation misinformation all kinds
of campaigns
and for example um the way that it's
it's coordinated
is so it's emergent but it seems so
deliberate
uh it's almost if they're acting in
unison i remember early on in the riots
this summer
after i had come back from covering
riots downtown and i come back and i'm
sitting on my back porch just debriefing
and i get an email from the pta
of my local school and the pta is
sending out a list of books to read from
the anti-defamation league and at the
top of the list
is white fragility and anti-racism and
they're saying hey
parents read these books and then tell
your kids to read them and you guys talk
about it around the dinner table
and it was there where it really just
hit me that i just had seen
on the ground an emergent conflict with
street warriors
setting buildings on fire throwing bombs
at cops attacking people destroying
property
committing felony after felony after
felony setting cars on fire
then i get home and i get an email
telling my kids that they're supposed to
read anti-racist and white fragility and
that's when it all just
boom it just collided in my head that
this is a war that's happening on
multiple levels
on a physical level on a mental level on
a moral level
it happens with kinetic energy it
happens with information
and it's in it happening in a
decentralized way which is something
that we all need to understand these
days decentralization is the theme
of the 2020s it will be the theme of the
2030s
it's because the last 50 years all we've
done is consolidate
and then expand and eliminate our
borders and our boundaries in a top-down
capacity but today the battle is
emergent and it's between
networks and the networks don't always
have allegiances
to nation states they have allegiances
to ideas and causes and
and missions and so it is happening
everywhere and i'm glad you brought up
the fourth generation warfare element
because if people will say things like
antifa is
is an idea well then so is isis and
isis operates in i think a similar
fashion in terms of its decentralized
network so what i'm asking you to
translate for us
is like how does this military doctrine
this fourth generation warfare
how does it like realize itself with
antifa how do they
how do they organize why is that
organization
form dangerous and uh how come we can
see
it all around us on every level at every
at every turn
basically right so there's one is the
sort of anarchist model of organization
which the core
level of you think of it as is your if
you're in a
structured military system as as your
fire team
your very smallest unit of organization
is
what the anarchists call an affinity
group which is literally just the people
with whom you have an affinity
uh meaning your friends people you like
people who agree with you
who have a shared vision of what you
want to do and then who go do it
that's it it's pretty basic but it's
pretty effective
and from there you can you can structure
affinity groups through various clusters
you can make
uh you can do decision making through
consensus which is how they do most of
their decision making is through
consensus building
uh through spokes councils what they
call spokes counsels
you saw people who watched the occupy
movement uh during that period saw this
happen in real time
and they thought it was kind of funny
and you know they made fun of it uh
with the microphone check and this that
the other thing but it is an effective
method of organizing for people
who who have a shared vision um
what they rally around is this thing
called the plausible promise right
like they see something that that's
possibly effective someone tries a
tactic
they see it's effective and they and
then they start to rally
around this idea that oh this thing that
we want to do is actually possible
right and so what is it that they they
want to do what is their plausible
promise what is rallying these affinity
groups
to come together and sort of copycat
each other's tactics get together into
these councils you're talking about
and then make their decisions that way
like what is their plausible promise at
this point
fundamentally it's to supplant and
overthrow the state
uh at the at the highest level um and
you see their their instinct to do that
with you know the capitol hill
autonomous zone
right as soon as it became possible they
had forced out the police
they established a zone and they tried
to govern a small polity
uh in accordance with their ideas didn't
last very long
but that's that was the goal and they
saw it and for a moment it lived
right you know and that's a very
powerful thing for an idea
that to say we had a space where we
existed in the real world
for a time and you made the connection
to isis and it was it was what part of
what made isis so dangerous
was their claim that we have established
the caliphate we have done it in the
real world
uh even if it only lives for a time yet
it is still lived
right and that it's a very powerful idea
um
and that they say you know we are living
our we are living our ideology we are
we are making our decisions in in an
anarchist
ideologically approved way uh and we can
show that it works
uh it works in the real world we can
outmaneuver the state we can outmaneuver
the cops
uh in this in this uh through the
through these means and it seems to be
working and so they they take that
seriously
uh and it bolsters them it makes them
feel like they're winning and by the way
i mean in my opinion they are winning uh
you know
have they do they win do they win a
single riot no
right that's that's the trick about the
police that's why the police are the
police is you always lose
uh because more police come and more
police come and more
state power comes uh and the more you
defeat them the more they respond until
eventually you're defeated
right but on the physical level but on
the ideological level
you're winning right so i
i've studied both rules for radicals
alinsky and the antifa handbook and i've
observed them
in practice and i think that there's
some element of
them knowing that the escalation that
they cannot win is still a victory for
themselves because
what they look for are weaknesses and
then points of attack where they can
elicit a response and so they find an
area
in which there's a weakness and in the
early days of the riots in dc
in 2020 the police park police national
guard etc they came
and formed a physical barrier with the
law enforcement around lafayette park to
keep people out there were no
fences there were no permanent barriers
and so it actually created this
very intense flash point right and so
they with their tactics and we can talk
about their riot tactics and
and the various members and and roles
that they have to play
but they would attack the the police and
just provoke and provoke and provoke and
provoke and all they really want is
is for the police to to overreact and to
respond in a way that
that that gives them another round of
energy and you can actually
feel when you're in the mob you can feel
the energy swells
and crests and you can feel them come
down and then you can tell where
the knight is headed by each additional
crest
having sort of a higher higher energy to
it
and so they just attack and provoke and
provoke an attack and it caused for a
huge
problem big disaster lots of conflict
and so
eventually the trump administration and
local police got smart and they took the
cops out of the way
and they put up physical barriers and
it's very difficult
for uh the antifa to get a response out
of a physical barrier and that actually
dispersed a lot of the energy so
it's interesting to see here how they
want to get a response sometimes they
get one that they like like they did
in portland at the federal courthouse
right this continuous antagonism
but then sometimes they get outsmarted
where you take the flash points away and
then they're basically just standing in
the middle of the street yelling at a
brick wall
but nevertheless they they do seem to be
winning
the messaging war at times what do you
think about that right now
where are we there with their messaging
war and the war of ideas and such
uh well that when i said i thought they
were winning that's where they're
winning they're winning in the messaging
war and they're
winning in the war of ideas uh the
example i would give for this
is the situation where uh
federal law enforcement in portland
started uh
making arrests of antifa organizers
after major protests
you know those who had been caught on
camera doing doing various violent acts
uh so they just uh instead of trying to
dive into the middle of the protest and
arrest the guy right there which is what
you would have traditionally done
they said let's not do that let's not
antagonize people
we'll make the arrest afterwards which
is a pretty i mean i understand logic
that's a pretty smart move
so what what does antifa do antifa turns
around
and films these arrests you know you've
got law enforcement guys snatching
people up
putting them in minivans uh you know
they're in an unmarked car
why because they don't want to start
another riot which is
you know if they were in a police car
the mob would have burned the police car
so that so they're in an unmarked car uh
and so antifa videotapes this
they say oh look unmarked you know
federal
militia trump troops are are arresting
us
uh they put that video on social media
it immediately gets grabbed by the
mainstream media which runs with it
um without a comment you know without
without any criticism or fact checking
uh and in fact stating things that were
factually untrue
like the the law enforcement individuals
were were unmarked
which is not true they did have markings
right uh and
then even so it's okay if they're
unmarked because hey that's that's
how things get done right yeah it's i
mean in fact that's not
not a requirement a lot of places i mean
they they i mean they have to say
they're police and
have a badge or whatever but a lot of
people get on get arrested by police in
suits all the time yeah ever heard the
phrase plain clothes i mean come on
pretty common but so mainstream media
runs with this claim
and then it gets echoed by you know
democratic senators
democratic members of the house
including the speaker of the house
and they organized an entire hearing on
it
uh you know or the the hearing that i
spoke at
before i spoke the previous panel was
the government panel
and the democratic senators proceeded to
grill
uh ken cuccinelli from from dhs for
hours about this factually untrue claim
that was promoted by antifa that that
by any uh by any metric is a huge
information operation win
right you have you have people who are
supposed to be on the other side
that is uh representing the us
government your opponent
uh speaking the words that you put in
their mouth
that's an operation that's an
information operation
yeah that's and that's how antifa
operates right because that feeds into
our claims that the opposition is
fascist are
true you know even look even the
democrat
democratic senators are saying that our
claims are true
that the trump regime is a fascist
regime and therefore
if the trump regime is a fascist regime
the only appropriate response is
anti-fascism yeah and so we feed people
back into the movement to support us
and then we can do the next operation
yep there's there's a continuous
feedback cycle and it
is really important for us to point out
the
media connection to antifa they can't
look it's it's one thing for guys like
me to just
run independent information uh outlets
and operations and try to
do our part to uh you know put what we
want out into the information space and
i think i'm doing a good job but i
don't have leading government officials
and politicians and the presidential
candidates
plus all of the mainstream
legacy media echoing and reinforcing
uncritically my claims that'd be great
thank you but
it's not happening yeah i'll take it
yeah but it's not happening so what do
you see is the connection between
legacy media and antifa why does there
seem to be a conduit between their
actions straight into the media right to
the government
back to the media and then straight into
american people's brains
why does it seem to flow so seamlessly
effortlessly
almost as if it's all planned and
coordinated
how what is the core what is the
connection there
so from my time studying uh
the islamists and the jihadists one of
the things i like to say with
is if everybody is on the same page
uh doctrinally you all have the same
doctrine
uh you all have the same ideology you
don't actually need a conspiracy
because everybody knows what their job
is right and so
you know when the antifa guys throw the
video up on social media
they know with certainty that you know
various
leftist reporters you know it may not be
the guys at the top level
you know at the wall street you know at
the washington post or new york times or
something
but you know the guys at slate the guys
at mother jones
uh you know guys yeah they're gonna run
it uncritically
right yeah and once it does it moves a
step up the legitimacy ladder
and then uh the washington post to the
new york times will
cite from you know from this leftist uh
you know blog or whatever it is you know
um
news outlet saying here's what happened
and they just cited uncritically
and then of course the the democratic
senators uh
will cite uh the washington post
uncritically
uh and so it's a they launder you
launder claims this way
through various levels of uh of
uh authenticity uh and and you get
different audiences
you know you have to reach different
audiences through different different
ways
um and you know media knows that they're
actively abetting aiding and abetting
this this organization
or do you think they're just like oh
this is the news i'm gonna report the
news
i don't think they think there's
anything wrong with it i mean look how
many blue checkmark
uh media reporters uh
will tweet out you know antifa just
means anti-fascist how can you be
against
anti-fascism or you know that they like
to do the thing where they they post the
picture from normandy and they say you
know our grandparents were anti-fascists
or
some such nonsense and um you know and
so if that's where your head is at
yeah why wouldn't you you know why
wouldn't you echo these claims
you know if if you're in the uh fiery
but mostly peaceful crowd
of cnn uh you know where all
all of these riots are just just
protests
then then you know you are pre-primed to
accept their
uh to accept their propaganda
uncritically and so you do
yeah and so what's great to point out
here is this again it's an emergent
phenomenon right it's
as much as it would be fun to be like
there's one guy with the marionette and
he's like taking control and guiding
everything
it's not this is an emergent network
phenomenon
they rally around a plausible promise
and an ideology and as you say you don't
need a conspiracy when
everybody knows the role that they're
supposed to play
that is a really excellent point because
it does feel like it's top down
coordinated but it really is what we're
experiencing what what john rob calls
network alignment we're watching an
alignment
between these networks of the
anti-fascists the networks of black
lives matter
and the critical race theory folks um we
are watching an alignment of the
corporations
uh the media and elements of the federal
government the blue
church is coined by jordan green hall
and so
these are very disparate groups but they
have a
common goal at the moment and they are
currently networked aligned
and that's around diminishing the power
of the federal government it's around
diminishing the
reputation and and branding if you will
of the federal government and of trump
and trump supporters
and interestingly uh uh in reading matt
stoller
and understanding the complete lack of
antitrust work that's been going on for
the last like four decades or so
it's interesting to see how there's an
alignment between the corporations
and the blue church and antifa and black
lives matter right now
because they're all kind of getting what
they want out of it
the corporations aren't getting messed
with on antitrust level
black lives matter and antifa are
getting their messages out there
and everybody just is is rallied around
uh calling donald trump a fascist and
anyone who supports him a fascist as
well
including me they called me a fascist
and a nazi and instead of going away
into the night here i
am we're going to bring even more
sunshine to disinfect this nonsense and
so
the current environment we've been while
the
while in the 60s the bombings and the
civil destruct
distress was much greater you know when
we've got presidents being assassinated
martin luther king getting assassinated
just cold-blooded killings i mean
although we've seen that now
and a thousand bombings on college
campuses we're seeing an escalation
now in tactics and in violence and
one of the things that really stood out
to me
was clearly what happened in portland
where it appeared that an antifa
kill squad basically took to the streets
in search of a trump supporter in a
group of people
they identified him they called him out
they were video recording it they shot
the guy right in the street they ran
away the guy had a place to go to he
bunkers down
with a machine gun and when the cops
finally come to get him
there's a crazy wild west shootout so
are we seeing an escalation in violence
are we seeing an escalation and tactics
do they train this stuff are there
people
who are like okay this is how we're
going to coordinate a kill team and then
do they practice do they think about it
because
i have looked at that video a million
times i interviewed a guy
who filmed it live we went over all the
footage and it's very clear that they
were moving in a coordinated fashion
they were in front of the target they
were behind the target
they blocked the road i mean it was
crazy what happened
are these people training are they
planning to escalate
how do they just how do they decide how
to do this talk us through that
sure so the first thing i think is worth
pointing out is that
they are a low intensity uh violence
and they're a low intensity insurgency
uh in terms of their violence
because that's a choice that they have
made right it's actually
um you think about it it's actually a
showing of
how dangerous and capable they are that
they're not more violent
because actually when you're when you're
jacking up your followers to to go fight
fascists and you're telling them
that any one of these trump supporters
could have a knife and they're going to
stab you
right which is what they tell they tell
people this all the time uh
you know or they tell people you know
why do you think we have seen so many
shootings
at these roadblocks and it's because
they have told their followers
white supremacists and cars are going to
run you over
and so they're jittery at the roadblocks
because they expect a white supremacist
to come run them over
right and when some civilian gets scared
and hits the gas
they shoot him because you know in their
mind
oh here's the white supremacist they
told me was going to come run me over
um and then of course you've got like
npr like uncritically running this
same claim right um but so
the fact that they're not more violent
uh is actually
an example of their organization and
their capability
i think we are seeing an increase in
violence i mean we're seeing an increase
in capability and tactics
um deploying these you know high-powered
lasers to blind people
deliberately blinding people is a
malicious wounding
in a lot of in a lot of states that
would be considered uh
justification for the use of lethal
force right uh
you know it's a serious act to
deliberately blind someone
uh throwing a molotov cocktail at
someone is a lethal act
you may not hit them but if you did it
would be potentially lethal
so they are certainly willing to engage
in lethal violence
uh the the killing of the of the trump
supporter
i i don't know how intentional it was
but they were clearly they were clearly
prepared to do that
and i think it's an example of
an insurgency that has established
themselves
as a shadow government and they have
space that they consider our space
whose streets who streets our streets
and so they genuinely believe that
portland belongs to antifa
and you you do not get to be a trump
supporter in portland that is their
position
uh i mean i don't know if you saw the
interview with the lady on the streets
of portland who
presumably seems just to be a civilian
but she was
you know she was completely unapologetic
and said well he shouldn't have been in
portland
uh it is uh for you know i've talked to
people that you know served in iraq and
served in afghanistan
and they'd say you know it's the same
thing or you know you talk to
uh you talk to peop law enforcement on
the gang squad
right and they'll say you know uh
if you belong to a group uh and you go
into the other groups area
a shooting will occur it is it planned
is it required to be planned
uh i mean there i i believe that was a
hasty ambush
uh in which case they saw him coming and
then were able to quickly prepare it
uh which again says something about
organization
and capability right but he was uh
he did not have a right to be there in
their view and they acted immediately
to resp to respond to it uh but the
question do they train yes they do
i mean we we've seen uh we know before
major protests they will encourage
people to attend
what they call non-violent uh training
but it's where they get a lot of this
practice for how to act as a human
shield
how to speak to police uh when you're on
the line
you know it's not you know you see the
same behavior from them whether you're
in dc or los angeles or chicago
uh they they speak in a certain way they
provoke in a certain way
and it's very effective by the way yes
um
and so all of that is trained and they
train you know de-arresting people from
the police
all of these things are trained in
advance right de-arresting that's when
the police grab a guy and then 10 people
swarm on the cop and drag their
antifa brother out of the law
enforcement's hands and
one of the videos that i saw that really
hammered home to me what was going on it
was back in the early days of george
floyd protest riots
and there was this guy who was just
filming what was going on on the street
he didn't seem to me to be a political
uh you know sort of participant and he
observed a group of four or five people
in a very systematic and coordinated way
bash in the windows of a car go get fuel
lighter fluid fluid or some sort of you
know light
igniter then they come back they fill in
the car
filled it up with a lighter fluid they
the guys
with skateboards were both coordinated
and then bashing in the front and back
windows and the side windows
and then one person goes away and then
comes back another person goes away
come back then they light the car on
fire and it all happens in a matter of
like one minute
and there was just no way that that was
something that was random or spontaneous
they had
the lighter fluid in their backpacks
they had the skateboards to use as
weapons
they moved one person in to do the demo
that person moved out someone moved in
to do the
you know plant the fuel and then someone
else came in and lit it
and it just happened so quickly and in
such an organized fashion there was
no question in my mind that they
practiced it
and in fact they might have even planted
the car in the street in the first place
beforehand because it was a cop car
that had been stripped of its sirens and
whatever and it was like why is it even
there
and so there's clearly coordination some
people speculate that the pallets of
bricks that were found around were part
of this coordination
i don't know so much about that but i do
see the tactics evolving
and it troubles me and you're right that
you can see these
uh replicated in any city that you go to
and i found a graphic once that was
basically mapping out the hong kong
protests
and there's all these different players
right you've got they call them the
mages or whatever the guys with the
laser pointers you've got
the light mages yeah light mages you've
got the people with the shields that are
up
in front they they actually manufacture
shields they have people that get
together and build them there you can
imagine they're having like a [ __ ]
picnic
and they're like you know just building
shield from building shields for the
battle tonight guys
and they've got these shield people and
then they've got people whose job it is
is to launch projectiles from from back
behind the lines
they've got people who are geared to be
medics they've got people with food and
water supplies
they've got eyes in the sky they've got
social media people
following all the police scanners all
twitter accounts public available
cameras they're reporting police
movements they're reporting the
movements of the other groups
they're calling people out for trainings
i mean it is a
whole system in place
and it moves from town to town it can
pop up anywhere
and we saw a very clear call
to action from people on the west coast
portland folks to move
to dc to start doing
you know laying a siege is what they
were saying and it wasn't just
speculation that they were moving across
the country
the van that was on the ground in
portland was on the ground in my
hometown of dupont circle i couldn't
believe it
i laughed when the cop walked up smashed
the window and dragged the guy out of
there
and then people who had been arrested in
oregon have been arrested in dc now
and so they're spreading they're
replicating
they're escalating and i'm starting to
wonder
now who's funding all this is there
funding
where does it come from where is the
money come from where does the support
come from
right so my experience has been
that most of the stuff that they bring
to the riots are relatively inexpensive
even the lasers and stuff not too
expensive
yeah uh and they sort of um
they sort of get better at this as they
go you know but you show up
somebody will hand you a shield do you
have any idea where the shield came from
you don't
but somebody will hand it to you and if
you want one if you'd be willing to
throw it somebody will hand you a
molotov cocktail
do you know where it came from you
probably don't but
if you're willing to throw them off
cocktail there will be one available for
you to throw
right those things aren't terribly
expensive
uh and they they get they're able to
raise a lot of money on on
some of these fundraising sites some are
deliberately ideological fundraising
sites
some of them are neutral uh fundraising
sites that just happen to let it go on
uh but that stuff doesn't cost a lot of
money what costs money is transportation
what costs money is logistics hotel
bills
uh there's a example of a there's a
hotel
out in uh just outside of dc
uh in one of the outlying counties which
has been the base of operations for
richmond and dc
uh according to what i've been told and
they've got
that information now offline i'd love to
know they've been they've been there for
uh they've been there for weeks yeah
hotel bills cost money and stuff cost
money
you know during the uh harassment of the
rnc
convention when they were coming out of
the white house a lot of the people
there said
uh the protesters or the harassers were
staying in the same hotel
yeah let's talk about that for one
second it's not it's not cheap
so where does that money come from let's
talk we'll come back i just have a story
to tell there i was there on the ground
that night
i was on 15th street between the white
house
and the hotel district right there and i
observed all these people coming out of
the white house and getting harassed on
the street and i guided them
away from the mobs into safety and then
at one point i noticed there was
rand paul was there and so i went up to
him and i was like rand you cannot be
here you're gonna get attacked
and then we found one cop we got him
behind a cop we waited for like 15
minutes the mob surrounded everybody we
waited for the police to come to escort
him away
and the next day i'm talking to rand's
people and they're telling me that they
could hear
in their hotel rooms through the walls
they could hear agitators organizing
talking about rand paul being in the
hotel
we came here to do this what are we
going to do how do we do this where is
he what
and he was totally uh blown away that
they were
you know paid to be put in the w hotel
one block away from the white house it
takes money it takes logistics it takes
planning now let's not just assume that
every antifa
scrub is completely poor there is an
ideological
connection to people with money who want
to support the same plausible promise
and so they're willing to contribute
money one of the ways that i've seen
them contribute a substantial amount of
money
it's not actually through cash but
in-kind service donations so what they
do is
is when they're getting ready to go out
to riot they're like okay here's the
phone number to call if you get arrested
tonight and they
with they have big black sharpies and
they all write the phone number on their
forearm
and the phone person at the other end of
that phone number
is a pro bono legal counsel who's there
to represent them get them off without
any bail get them back
out on the street and then represent
them if something something happens to
them in court down the road and so when
you can
operate with a sense of relative
impunity
that is as as powerful as giving
somebody like a million bucks
if you know that you can go out get
arrested have a lawyer
have a medical team have food supplies
have your bombs there your shields there
your bricks there have people with your
back
looking out for you on social media and
cameras and security and stuff
you basically are experiencing the
benefits of being a part of an actual
sort of national mobilized military
force
without it having to be a top down
controlled there's a general and a
colonel or whatever
controlling all the troops and so this
funding is something that we really
i think need to track and we need to
watch what else have you seen in terms
of
crowdfunding or money from abroad has
any money from international sources
come into play here
sure so uh the numbers on the let's
start with the numbers on the arm that
that's almost always the national
lawyers guild uh which exists for this
purpose
right they uh they they exist to bail
out rioters and protesters
and they have uh since the 50s
uh bailed out and defended subversives
and
and revolutionaries since they were
founded by members of the communist
party
uh in the united states uh so that's
their role
right and then you've got the bail funds
that are being set
set up to bail people out right which
which are flush with millions and
millions of dollars
uh out of out of the black lives matter
movement so you have
you have the black lives matter various
black lives matter organizations and
they're supporting
a variety of different groups but
especially these bail funds
and then tons of money flowing into them
from corporations
from left-wing foundations
hundreds of millions of dollars a lot of
money i i was
i heard two billion dollars yeah uh over
the past
several months i don't know if that's
exactly right but
but we're talking serious cash uh
some of it's going to go missing some of
it's going to to end up
in or or go missing uh
into the right hands or wrong hands
depending on how you look at it
uh and so one of the things that i've
been pushing really hard at looking at
is how does this money move
from uh these quasi-respectable
actually i should say they are really
respectable they would be considered
more respectable than me
uh the tides foundation uh the open
society foundations
um these sorts of really afford
foundation really
large uh well-funded foundations
how does money from them end up in these
other groups well i'll give you
an example that i used in my testimony
that i think is illustr
illustrative which is how is refused
fascism funded
refused fascism is a front organization
of the revolutionary communist party
uh but and you see these guys at a lot
of these protests
um and they
uh were for a time their fiscal sponsor
was a group called the alliance for
global justice
the alliance for global justice uh is a
non-profit out of phoenix arizona
that funds a lot of different groups by
acting as their fiscal sponsor
and what that means is they're a
registered 501c3 that can receive tax
deductible donations
from any foundation and most foundations
have to
they have to give money to a registered
501c3 they can't just give money to any
bomb on the street
so money moves from the foundations to
the fiscal sponsor which is alliance for
global justice in this case
now alliance for global justice used to
be the nicaragua
network which was an organization set up
to support the sandinistas
in the 80s back back when we were
fighting communist insurgencies in latin
america
but they've transitioned to the alliance
for global justice they support over a
hundred different groups
as their fiscal sponsor one of which was
refused fascism and money flows from the
from these organizations
from these foundations into the 501c3
fiscal sponsor
which then in turn distributes them to
the less reputable groups
like the revolutionary communist party
we know that from videos that were done
by project veritas
that groups like refuse fascism seem to
know uh
where the original money came from uh
there's a video
that the project veritas released where
they talk about getting money from open
society
uh to support refuse fascism for example
so there seems to be some coordination
there but it's all very clean
so i've urged uh legislators to look at
this
fiscal sponsorship arrangement to to
figure out how to
better track where money actually goes
after it goes into the hands of the
fiscal sponsor and then
off to to some un um you know some group
that doesn't have
any kind of charter or any kind of uh
official organization so there's
international money there's corporate
money
there's money from soros there's money
from
freaking nike there's money from bank of
america i remember was a big contributor
uh there's ties to communists and and is
are there ties to
islamists as well i mean this is this is
like a global
network of funding and organization and
transmission i mean
when someone says this is an idea what
does an idea need funding what does an
idea need for a training what does an
idea
need for bail funds and medics
and and and eyes in the sky and
intelligence networks if they're not
coordinating
action by the way guys the idea antifa
is anti-fascist action it's like the
idea is to take action
but we can say who we can say is an idea
but it's an idea to do something
yeah that's a good point so when they
say well you know it's just an idea to
be anti-fascist
like well it's an idea to take action
right and that's that's the fundamental
point
right and right you know you talk about
the intelligence or or the different
elements
and one of the ways that they achieve
this is through this concept of
diversity of tactics
right so you may be somebody that
believes what antifa believes
uh but you don't have the guts to pick
up a shield or throw a molotov cocktail
they're okay with that that's fine can
you are you really good with computers
do you know how to dox people
all right that's your job right you know
do you know how to track social media
and okay that's your job they're they're
all about
do what you are do what you are
comfortable doing
for the movement right and and this is a
really powerful concept and it allows
you to
uh mobilize a larger group of people
than you would get if you were
you know some kind of strict terror
group and you're like okay
if you want to join us off to
afghanistan you go uh
pick up a kalashnikov you're like whoa
whoa that's not you know i want to help
you but that's not how i want to help
you
uh you get a lot further with this kind
of diversity of tactics
we will find a way to fit you into the
network right
and they do that is an interesting point
it's almost as if they've raised the
militia they have raised the militia
they are working in coordination uh
to fight against this spirit of america
the american power and presence within
their own country like oh crazy there's
american
might within its own country let's
attack it uh but what's fascinating also
is that there
is a response to this you know we people
are raising up their own militias and i
don't necessarily mean physical i mean
information militias we see it happening
uh we see the sort of emergence of a
counter force
in terms of the information space this
is an example of an emerging
force against the the information space
and i'm wondering you know as their
tactics increase
and enforce and then scope and become
more refined
what the response is gonna be from the
people
and what the response is gonna be from
the government so let's talk a little
bit about that like
what does the government really know i
heard
ray the other day say that uh
white supremacists are the biggest
threat we face domestically a bunch of
horse crap there
what do they really know at dhs and at
the fbi
and what does the trump administration
really know
and what are they actually doing if
anything
and then after we talk about all that
let's talk about what we should be doing
so
what what is happening right now what
does the government know
for sure and what kind of action are
they taking
well i'll say uh certainly they know
less than they should
uh we can start with that uh the
i think the attorney general has been on
point uh
bill barr he seems to get this you know
some of his statements
early on he said these are revolutionary
groups right that's an important
statement from the attorney general
if the attorney general says you are a
revolutionary group
that your group seeks to overthrow the
government of the united states
you don't that's actually not something
you're allowed to do believe it or not
uh we haven't enforced the law in that a
long long time
but as a matter of fact as they say the
constitution is not a suicide pact
and and there are elements uh that allow
the government to defend itself from
those who would overthrow the
constitution
so it's important when he says things
like that uh
i think president trump himself gets it
on sort of an instinctive level
when he said at the debate when uh joe
biden said this is just an idea and he
said
they will overthrow you joe right he
understands at some sort of instinctive
level
what they are and i thought that was
very positive
director ray has i've just not been
impressed
uh the fbi ironically the fbi was
founded in part to respond to
anarchist insurrections uh you know in
the earliest in the 1920s you had like
the palmer raids in the 1920s to arrest
anarchists and communists
who were conducting a small bombing
campaign so this is the fbi's bread and
butter or at least it's supposed to be
and yet they've been really bad on it uh
you saw that their
their primer on what they call anarchist
extremism which is how they define
uh antifa or any group like it uh
you know it says these are just
individuals uh
anarchism is fine as long as there's no
action to overthrow the state
they say you know most of the laws that
these guys break
are local laws and therefore local
law enforcement is responsible for
dealing with it
well now that's true if you believe that
the individual who smashed in that car
and set it on fire
uh all he did was commit arson and
vandalism those are local crimes that is
true
but if you understand that he did it in
a co
in alignment with a movement that is
seeking to overthrow the constitution
well guess what that's a federal crime
that's a federal responsibility
to defend the constitution and to defend
the state government
from an insurrectionary force that seeks
to seeks to
displace it so those are federal crimes
and if you understood
uh antifa correctly you would understand
that those are federal crimes
uh bill barr you know he had a
conversation with some of his
prosecutors and he said we should be
looking at seditious conspiracy
uh as a potential avenue towards making
arrests
a seditious conspiracy uh it sounds like
it's about sedition and things that you
you know say against the government in
fact it has nothing to do with what you
say against the government
has has to do with what you do against
the government and if you
assault a federal building if you uh
deliberately and through violence
prevent federal law enforcement or
federal officials from doing their jobs
that is a uh federal crime known as and
you conspire to do it with other
individuals
that's that's a federal crime known as
seditious conspiracy and you go to jail
you can go to jail for 20 years for that
it's a serious offense
so there are laws that we can use uh but
they require that you understand
that there's a level of organization
involved
that's interstate that is uh conspiring
in the realist sense of the term the
real sense of the term uh you have to
understand that if you don't admit that
then you can't deploy these tools
because they require a conspiracy
uh between multiple individuals and they
require a goal
of seeking to overthrow the state uh do
you think
if you think if you think these are
social justice protests
uh then then you you
you completely negate those tools and
you ignore them
do you think that the people who we
count on to defend us the constitution
our property federal property and let's
not forget that like defending life and
property is
what police and law enforcement are
supposed to do
and they train the police and law
enforcement to consider property as an
important thing to protect his life
because hey
this is freaking america and that's what
we're all about it's protecting
personal property and privacy and
property right it's second only to life
and liberty
right exactly and so do you think that
the people that we're supposed to be
relying upon within the federal
government to protect us
and to to to to put down these types of
insurgencies
are they ignorant are they dumb are they
co-opted are they guilty i mean i'm
getting to the point now where i'm
thinking you're either
you're either with us or here against us
in this regard
meaning you can't there's no there's no
chance that a national security official
is ignorant of what's happening here
unless they're willfully ignorant so
that's my take what's your take like do
these people know what the hell is going
on
are they just being stupid are they
getting played are they on the other
side
what's happening uh i think there's a
big uh
swing i will tell you for certain that
there
are federal agents that get this that
want
nothing better than to be let off the
leash to do what they do
and bring these guys down uh i can tell
you that there are law enforcement
officers
who know nothing of what i told you
about the history of antifa
where it came from or what it's for and
what it does and how it operates
but they'd like to know uh they're not
getting that information but they would
like it and if they got it they would do
the right thing
uh there are absolutely uh
people in the government that genuinely
believe
that um essentially the
the idea behind the protesters is right
that you know somehow this is justified
uh and they don't want to take action
they want to deal with other
other things that they consider genuine
threats right you see
that's part of why you get this giant uh
you know a white supremacy is the
largest threat uh
in part because as you know we've talked
about critical race theory and other
things that they've
they've pushed into academia and so
forth um
if you believe that then you believe
white supremacy is everywhere
well then certainly white supremacy
would be the largest threat wouldn't it
right uh and it also it comes from you
know they count the way they count up
uh who you know what groups killed who
and so on so forth
to say well you know a white supremacist
killed 24 people
you know that adds up to a pretty large
total and if you're only interested in
deaths if you're only paying attention
to
who is killed then you might say well
that's the greatest threat but that's
not actually your responsibility
as as a federal law enforcement officer
your fundamental responsibilities to the
defense of the constitution
and so the group that poses the largest
threat to the constitution
and to the government that that
constitution creates
that is the largest threat that is the
threat you are most responsible for
dealing with
and if you approach it in those terms
then i think it's undeniable
that antifa is a larger threat than
white supremacy
but they have not been trained to think
in those terms for many many years
yeah i wonder what we can do to spread
awareness i mean i'm doing everything
i can i talk to people in the
administration i know that there are
some people who
quote get it i know that there's some
people that totally understand the
fourth generation warfare aspects that
are happening here
they understand network alignment they
understand plausible promises they
understand
that antifa is an actual physical terror
group that they kill
people they destroy buildings they use
intimidation and violence as a way to
advance
political causes as a way to strike fear
and terror
in the citizenry which i believe are the
definitions of terrorism
right there and it just astonishes me
the lack of ignorance or not the lack
the the depth of the ignorance
uh across basically everywhere
on this matter and and i liken it as
well to
you know just like your regular mom in
bethesda who's like black lives matter
yeah of course black lives matter i
think that's great but she has no idea
that black lives matter is marxist
organization that believes in the
destruction of the nuclear family
and the breakdown of anything outside of
your outside of yourself the breakdown
of
any tied anything greater any
nationalism any patriotism
your community your family they want to
destroy all of that but hey black lives
matter for sure and there's signs in
their yards and
they tell their teenage daughters black
lives matter and such so
i think that the information and warfare
has been tremendously successful
on antifa's part in black lives matter's
part
and to the point where they're able to
rally foot soldiers that know
not what they really do and uh you know
i tried to tell my normie friends like
capital b capital l capital n black
lives matter
lower case b l m black lives matter yeah
right like there's a big difference
and people don't understand it and i'm i
fall into this trap sometimes where i
forget that i'm like
down deep in the trenches and these
niches and in these subcultures and i've
been following them for years i've been
living their tactics
engaging with them they've chased me
around the city calling death threats at
me and they've chased down my little
league team and all these things so
to me it's like oh this is common
knowledge but i just don't think that
the knowledge
is out there and of course we're
fighting against the media and the
politicians and
oh my god the i can't remember his name
right now ellison the guy from minnesota
holding up the antifa handbook and like
you know maybe he doesn't even know what
he's doing all these people are just
stooges and i think we forget that
people out there are just dumb even our
politicians are dumb or
some of our national security people are
dumb and they just kind of roll with
what they're given it's tough to be
critical
and and challenge what seems to be a
dominant idea
and and it's hard to be counter to the
to the mainstream
and it takes balls and it takes a
certain
certain risk structure in your life i
guess to take to take a
counter position you have to be
supported if you're gonna get attacked
etc
um so i'm a little disappointed with the
response but i
i am encouraged in some degree to
trump's recent rhetoric
right like i think beginning back with
the
mount rushmore address it became very
clear
that he was was latching on to this
to the idea that blm and antifa and
critical race theory is anti-american
it's anti-founding
it it promotes a notion of justice that
runs contrary
to the justice that was established by
the founders
thank you claremont i've been learning
about that along the way
uh and um it's just clear that he's
adopted that language
and in a very eloquent and powerful way
with the rhetoric
and he's continued it on with his uh
attacks on critical race theory in the
federal government thank you christopher
ruffo who was also on this show last
week or two weeks ago
and it does seem to me that he's taking
this as attack this is why i voted for
him in the first place was to
to fight against critical race theory we
call it just intersectionality or
radical feminism like four or five years
ago
um but they're still not doing enough
when i go
downtown to lafayette square 16th and h
northwest washington dc
and i see black lives matter painted on
the street and letters big enough to see
from outer space
i see black lives matter banners hanging
off the buildings that were had
just recently been destroyed and
attacked
by black lives matter i see the flags
hanging
i hear the drums beating i watch
coordinated people
in the street teams attacking the police
in a systematic way that was replicated
from other locations they've got their
flags they've got their music they've
got the city
it's on a place called black lives
matter plaza
right it's like we're obviously not
doing enough
we're obviously not doing enough and so
my question to you now it kyle
is what do we do what do we do as
citizens
what do we do as independent information
sort of soldiers what do we do as
a nation how do we split the insurgency
is it is it a given that the
corporations black lives matter and
antifa are going to be in alignment
forever i don't think so what do we do
what do we do kyle uh well i always
start with
the fact that you can't fight something
with nothing
and so if the reason why these guys are
so effective is because they know what
they believe
they they have their vision of what
justice is
and they stick to it and their their
view of justice is fundamentally
opposite
of ours if i if we're in alignment with
the founder i mean think about how they
made it
impossible to say all lives matter
what could be truer a
and b what is more fundamental to
the american way of life and our
understanding of the world
than all lives matter isn't all lives
matter
sort of the same thing as saying all men
are created equal
indeed uh right and so uh ours is fun
you know they say well why can't you say
that black lives matter if black lives
are a part of all lives well that is
factually true
so all lives matter works uh if i say
all lives matter then
inherently all black lives also matter
um but to to say that
one set to be focused on categories to
break people down into categories is to
attack the principle
that all men are created equal which is
the fundamental attack on our view of
justice
yeah so if we we have to start from
there we have to educate ourselves there
as to what it is we believe
and then we have to live our doctrine in
the same way that they choose to live
their doctrine
right so that will ground us in a place
where we are prepared
to take action and then we have to
educate people
i think it's really important to speak
especially to
uh law enforcement and to uh
military uh active duty and veterans
about what their responsibilities are to
the constitution
what their um you know what their why
their powers are derived from the
constitution uh
and how they have a responsibility to
defend the constitution
against all enemies foreign and domestic
and
if you say you know so what is the root
cause of your purpose
right as a police officer standing on
that line when that guy is
yelling at you or that gal is yelling at
you you have to be able to fall back on
this notion
that i understand why i am here and the
role that i am playing in the defense of
my country
so that's that is a bare minimum if we
can't do that
uh we can't do anything well having done
that we then have to institutionalize
that
uh we have to move up the chain with law
enforcement federal state and local
and have them understand you have a
responsibility to defend
the constitution you have a
responsibility to defend the public you
have responsibility to defend
the property of the public because of
these
beliefs and principles that we have uh
and
you have to understand you have a
responsibility to educate yourself
as to why these threats are threats to
that
uh and we can help you do that you know
uh i've i've been able to do a number of
briefings to law enforcement and
on antifa uh if you have any active duty
law enforcement guys that want one
uh or have can get a group together to
do one i'm happy to do that
uh you have a responsibility as you know
sun tzu says to know the enemy and know
yourself
uh so one educate yourself about
yourself about what it is
you believe and then two educate
yourself on the enemy and what they
believe
and i believe if you understand what
they believe you will unders be able to
get in their head you'll be able to see
how they operate and you'll be able to
beat them
you know that's why i ultimately spend
all this time talking about
ideology and this set and the other
because if i understand what
the way you view the world i can
understand how you'll respond to
different stimuli
and then i can try to beat you or more
importantly i can teach other people how
to
how to beat you i firmly believe in this
know the enemy
know thyself i recently had alexander
dugan
the russian political philosopher and
geopolitical theorist
on the podcast people ask me why i was
giving him any airtime or putting him on
my platform
and the reason why is because you got to
know what they're thinking
you got to know what everybody is
thinking you know dugan is a
is an interesting character on a number
of levels but primarily you want to just
know what they're thinking about in
moscow like
you want to know what their goals are
and their frame of reference are so that
you can
be better equipped to manage any future
conflict
and you can also better understand who
we are
at the same time by comparison and so
knowledge is very important here and
information
very important here but what do we do
once
once we understand let's just assume
the administration understands the
threat let's assume
that you know a significant enough of
the citizen population understands the
threat
what do we do from there do we just
arrest them as they commit crimes do we
infiltrate them
what do we do what do we do yeah the
answer that is yes
uh actually the uh the u.s government
historically
federal law enforcement historically has
been really good
at fighting these types of threats you
know uh most people
think about the fbi's defeated the ku
klux klan
in the 1960s when they conducted
bombings against black churches and
those kinds of things
but in fact the fbi started targeting
the klu klux klan in the 1920s
not because they were terrorists but
because they were a threat to the
constitution
they were seen as a subversive group
targeting the constitution and so
they were investigated for those reasons
uh and we have to get back to that we
have to get back to
law enforcement operating on the basis
of defending the constitution
and and the american founding principles
that are derived from it
uh so that if you want if you understand
the world in that way that will enable
you to make case
larger cases right follow up uh you said
infiltrating infiltrating antifa is
quite difficult
because it is so decentralized because
it is so well networked
but it is possible uh we have done it
before
uh in other in other contexts it is it
is doable
but take the you have to first of all
know or believe that there's a
conspiracy worth infiltrating and
investigating
in order to do that but we have the
capacity to do that if we want to do it
we can do it
then you know if we wanted to we've been
talking about antifa solely domestically
the reality is they operate in a number
of different countries
uh all throughout western europe and
another number of other places there are
antifa groups
that makes them an international threat
they move money
internationally they have the
international antifa defense fund
which collects money from various
countries and moves it internationally
to other countries
you could make you could make the case
that antifa
is a foreign terrorist organization on
the basis of their international
ties uh which would give you a number of
tools
uh that we can apply to foreign
terrorist organizations that we don't
apply
to domestic terror uh is that the right
move
i'm not certain it's it would be worth i
think having the argument and having the
discussion
there are a number of other law
enforcement tools that exist to target
groups
that intend to overthrow the government
you are not
supposed to be able to immigrate or get
a visa to enter the united states
if your goal is to overthrow it that's
actually in the law
it's not enforced very much anymore the
trump administration actually just
recently announced
that they were going to start enforcing
the uh law which prohibits visas or
immigration
on the basis of membership in a
totalitarian party
so if you are a communist uh you are not
supposed to be able to get a visa to
enter the united states
that would be somewhat helpful um so
there are laws on the books that can be
used
you just have to have the will to use
them and over the past
uh you know um we defeated the
communist urban insurgencies of the of
the 1970s and 80s
but shortly after we did there was an
attack on all of these tools of
government that the government used
against those groups uh and they were
mostly removed or taken away
but we do know how to do this and it can
be done we just have to
you have to be willing to spend the
political capital to use some of these
laws
and then say you know when you
inevitably get challenged as you will
by the national lawyers guild and the
aclu and
all these other networks uh of leftist
lawyers that exist
to oppose these things they will sue you
and you will have to fight them
in court and you have to be prepared and
willing to do that and
no president has been willing to do it
yet uh
trump might be that guy he's done things
that i didn't think
were possible uh and so we may see that
he's willing to do that he certainly
uh understands i think that he has a
duty to to defend these things
yeah let's play cynic for a sec
not too hard is there any advantage to
letting antifa play out their
their nonsense in the street does it
does it help
let's say our cause is preserving the
constitution and the spirit of the
founding
is there any advantage to letting antifa
run its course a little bit right now
i can see a number of reasons why that
might be true um
from a law enforcement perspective
especially if you're trying to get to
the to the top of things
uh if you're infiltrating if you're if
you're tracking and
collecting the signals and all of these
different things the longer it plays on
the more data you collect and this is
the co this is the constant challenge
right this is the challenge between
uh law enforcement and district
attorneys
and intelligence guys you know do we
stop them right now to prevent more
violence and trouble that's the
sort of average law enforcement response
uh do we let this play on so i have a
little bit more evidence to show the
jury
that's the typical district attorney
response and then you have the
intelligence responses let's just see
where it goes because the more i see the
more i collect
and the more i know and so these things
are all intention and you have to make
decisions on the basis of it
i think if i had a confidence that that
was
happening that we were we were doing
that sort of collection and we were we
were building those sorts of cases
i would say let it play on uh
on the other hand um i'm not so sure
they're doing that
yeah and i think there is a there's a
hunger from the american people
uh to see law order restored and i think
the candidate that does that
will be uh you know the candidate who
convinces the people that he can do that
will uh will be the guy that wins and
right now you have
uh president trump who takes the
position that he is the law and order
man
and that he's going to be hard on you
know these anarchists and terrorists
and then you have joe biden who
and the democrats who have taken a sort
of
um how do i put this in the most
non-partisan way
um there's an element of
um you know nice story you have there it
would be a shame if anything happened to
it
uh an element of extortion where
we we know these guys and we can make
this all go away
if you just do what we want right uh and
that's the
that's the political fight uh and that's
i mean
you know that's not my instinct i'm
pretty sure it's not your instinct jack
but for a lot of people that is a
powerful uh motivation
that oh if i go along to get along all
of this will go away
right uh and that is i think the fight
yeah and
that's definitely the approach that
they're taking vote for us or else
is the subtext of that as well um
i think that there's some advantage uh
in the long term game
to having as much of antifa on display
blm on display as possible our challenge
is that of course the mainstream media
does not pick up on this stuff doesn't
distribute it
you know continues to push like michelle
obama
yesterday or two days ago giving her a
whole speech about how isn't it violence
anyway isn't it interesting how these
uh riots have disappeared right you know
you and i follow social media and guys
like andy know
and the other guys in portland if you if
you follow those guys you know
these things are still happening every
single night
right and the media for a while found it
advantageous to show you that
uh and you'll remember in the early days
they showed all of this stuff
and that was when they were trying to
move the overton window towards
uh defund the police but when it became
clear that it was not helping them
politically
uh you know you had don lemon who
explicitly said this uh
it's not good for the polls this stuff
needs to stop right
and then the media just stops reporting
it so i'm sure there are people out
there who think that the riots have
ceased
in fact they have not seized they have
not not in the least
and in dc just to be totally
perfectly clear they have there has been
a little
they have subsided some the at the end
of may early june was the most amount of
property damage that i saw
uh the most amount of arson violence
looting
um and and attacks on the police
but they've shifted their tactics now
and they always will right the response
and tactics is a dialectic they go
into concert with each other they
respond to each other and they create
their own sort of trajectory based on
the response of the counterparty
and what they've done now is instead of
just attacking federal buildings or
whatever because they've taken the
police
away they start going into into uh you
know
neighborhoods and they start going into
restaurants and eateries and they
this is kyle this is part of the reason
why i got to get out of washington dc
just
literally walking distance the closest
commercial strip to my house
i've been to this restaurant before they
went the group they come up the street
they go to the restaurant outside the
people sitting on the patio
they come over the fence they get in
your face and they scream at you and
they say
raise the fist black lives matter if you
don't you're a racist and you're okay
with that and then you have 50 people
screaming at you
you've got the other patrons saying just
say it just say it make them make them
leave
and you know the tactics evolve and
change
and so what i'm hoping to see
is that just like with critical race
theory right now
the parents of america are starting to
get hip to this right
they're starting to understand that when
they get the email about the adls book
reading list and courageous
conversations and we're just going to
have a talk about race
that that's not as benign as it sounds
everybody remembers doing current events
in school i always love current
events but today it's like
indoctrination events courageous
struggles struggle sessions etc
and the response i'm getting from
american parents is just
um incredible like they're they're
they're scared
they're starting to see it they're
starting to understand they're starting
to push back
people in my area are coordinating
there's parent groups that are evolving
i get emails
every day from people jurisdictions all
around the country who are starting to
see this stuff
and then when they see that blm antifa
terrorists go into the neighborhoods and
harass people
and and and force them to submit to
their will
and they make it so like guys like me i
don't even we decide where to go out to
eat based on
what what's the what's the riot you know
rating tonight are we gonna is there a
chance of riots is it gonna rain
where should we go you know i'm not
kidding either we deliberately pick
where to go
where we're going to avoid this kind of
confrontation
and i think i'm hoping that the more
that we bring attention to this and the
more that they do dumb [ __ ] like attack
uh you know just regular folks going out
to dinner
um that they will begin to lose the
information
war a little bit and that they will not
only
lose the the moral element that they
have but they're going to motivate
people to defend their children
and to defend their homes and their
neighborhoods so
there is some benefit i think to
letting it play out a little bit but
then when you start talking about people
getting killed
i mean we're up to like 35 or 36 people
murdered and killed during the summer
riots
billions of dollars of property
destruction
um you know it's a tough game to play to
say oh just let them go kill some more
people so that we can beat them in the
end
um so it's a tough thing to strategize
uh and you know my my job thankfully
isn't to come up with the ultimate
solution but to discover this
information disseminate the information
get it out there
get it onto youtube get it into facebook
get it into people's
living rooms and into their brains
and hopefully that will start to have
some effect what is your prognosis
kyle what do you think is going to
happen
in the next four months between now
election and inauguration
and then depending on who wins which way
do you see the winds blowing after that
uh that's a really good question so just
i wanted to comment on the struggle
session part
uh and the thing that worries me about
allowing that to play on
is they did struggle sessions for a
reason
which is that they know if they make you
raise the fist and say black lives
matter
uh cognitive dissonance in your brain
which is a psychological effect that
happens right
you will try to orient your statements
and your actions with what you really
believe
and uh you know psychologists have shown
that people will orient what they
believe uh
in order to explain what they did right
and so
they will say well i i made the i made
the black lives matter fist it must be
because that's what i believe
uh and this i mean this is a real thing
that totalitarian states count on
yeah and and and play upon so there's a
reason why they do that and there's
there is a there is a real risk that
that will uh
work on some people right because the
counter psychology
is uh oh i am just weak and i got
bullied
right so what do you which nobody wants
to be right exactly yeah
uh so longer term i think um
despite comments from various democratic
party leaders in the media that this
stuff needs to
kind of simmer a little bit i don't
think it will
um i don't think they i think the the
antifa guys know that they're on a roll
and they're going to keep going
and i don't think that the democratic
party has enough authority to stop them
and they cannot they cannot alienate
them
one because fundamentally they believe
the same things
they have the same understanding of
justice and they sort of buy
these social justice claims and so they
have no room to argue with them
and two they believe i think uh
that the election will come down to
uh as the transition integrity project
called it a street fight
uh for those of you not familiar the
transition integrity project is this
so-called
bipartisan group of democrats and never
trumpers
who did a war game to try to figure out
what would happen
in various election scenarios and
at least in one of them it came down to
a real
quote unquote street fight with protests
and so on
where the democrats were literally
trying to drive uh the president from
office
uh because the president believes uh
that he had won
and that the democrats had cheated or uh
the democrats were trying to force the
matter through revolutionary politics
and so if they bel if they believe uh
and i didn't do the study they did the
study
but if they believe it then they will
need all
elements of their coalition and they
will need especially those elements of
their coalition that
provide uh street politics and and
physical revolutionary force
and so they cannot alienate blm and
antifa
uh so much so that they can't count on
them
when they need them that so they are in
a bind and when the president told
uh joe biden that they will overthrow
you uh i think you saw that very clearly
and all plus uh the democrats um
are totally weakened because uh
the democratic socialists of america
which are aligned with antifa
have made strong inroads into the party
uh they very successfully
primary a number of people this is where
you get alexandria ocasio-cortez in new
york
she's out of dsa and several other
members of the squad are also dsa
so if you're nancy pelosi you know
you cannot uh go so far
from from your revolutionary left uh or
your you risk losing people to primaries
uh
and you risk uh being slandered and
attacked by the same media
uh that you usually count on so
so the the establishment democrats have
put themselves in a bind
where they need these people uh and they
don't have the
they don't have the power or the
influence to reject them yeah that's
interesting uh counter example
donald trump explicitly disavows white
supremacy kkk proud boys even even
though i dispute that last one
it's fine for him to just say that just
to get the media off his back
and i believe that he means it i know
that everybody that i'm
uh you know uh hang out with on the maga
right we all disavow white supremacy
nazis all that [ __ ] to the far right
but yet the center-left folks don't
disavow
their radical left not only do they not
disavow them they count out to them
they give them what they demand they're
afraid of them
and i think we can all clearly feel the
fact that the democratic left is being
controlled manipulated by their
their radical left wing their tyranny of
the minority
their party is being jerked radically to
the left
which is why i am now uh i
i'm def i'm not an old school republican
by any means i voted democrat my whole
life i support donald trump and the
mission that donald trump is on
uh and that's because in part because
the radical left yanked the democrats so
far leftward
that they left guys like me standing in
the middle
all alone and then i realized that uh
you know the
the basic common american themes and
rights that i believe in
are actually at jeopardy under if if the
radical
left which is not even so radical
anymore continues to take power and
we've seen the impact
that a minority can have on our
institutions the
people have taken over science they've
taken over the academia they've taken
over the american psychological
association the united nations
they've taken over every friggin
institution in america through small
numbers
of just extreme effort and then they
change the policies and procedures which
have a whole systematic
systemic rather uh um impact
and so it's a good counterpoint to say
if you are a centrist and you're a
trumpist you're like look we reject our
radical right
the center left does not reject their
radical left
and so we know that if they win they're
going to give in to them they're going
to try to do the green new deal
and all the nonsense that goes with that
they're not going to fight critical race
theory they're not going to push back
against blm and antifa
in fact they're only going to get more
powerful so let me ask you kyle this
will be the last question we can wrap
up here tremendous tremendous podcast so
far thank you so much this information
has been really valuable it's been a lot
of fun yeah so
uh what happens trump wins what does blm
and tifa do
biden wins what does blm intifa do
so i think if trump wins
first of all we're going to see a lot of
activity from them in between the period
where the election is held and the
president is inaugurated i would
definitely expect
the same kind of g20 stuff we saw in
only more so this time around if the
president
wins again um i think they will continue
to push for a while
uh and eventually they will either be
suppressed or they will quiet down
if they feel like they're not having an
effect and they'll they'll take the
things that they learned uh this time
around
they will uh put them into their
doctrines
and next time they feel it's in
advantageous to take to the streets they
will do so
uh having learned all the lessons of
this past year
if biden wins um i think
that you see agitation continue uh
especially in order to push uh biden
to the left uh we've seen statements
from bernie sanders
alexandria ocasio-cortez
harris herself that indicated that they
know
that biden can be pushed to the left and
so they're going to need to do that
so they'll push him further and further
to the left they'll demand
certain appointments uh for the for the
radical left
uh and they'll they'll probably get them
uh
the actual violence on the street may
die down
uh once they get that uh and they will
again
um be prepared and ready for the next
time that they're needed
to to force uh their to force their
demands
or ultimately uh on you know unseat
biden
and and take charge that is that is
their goal
and their hope um and it's not
impossible you know if we if we are in
as
the antifa type certainly believe if we
are in an
age of revolutionary politics uh this
stuff has worked before
if you look at the 1948 uh coup
in czechoslovakia the communists
agitated and they pushed the socialists
on the left
to give them more positions and more
power and more influence and
and they took more and more authority
and they took over policing and they
took over
justice and they took over in various uh
departments
and then when they had everything that
they needed uh they
they pushed the socialists out of the
way and they took control
that is the way they view the world is
are they there yet i don't know
uh i think uh america is stronger than
that
at least i hopeful i'm hopeful that it
is but that is the way they view the
world uh
and so i believe that that is what they
would seek to do if if the opportunity
arose
yeah unfortunately it sounds like things
are gonna get worse for a little bit
before they get better
with trump you probably will see antifa
blm have a crazed spasm reaction
in protest um i i'm anticipating
election night through january to be
pretty
pretty busy and then if he does get
inaugurated holy crap they're gonna try
to burn down the whole city
um and then maybe trump can take care of
them from there or they double down and
they get even crazier and then who knows
what happens if the democrats win
sorry go ahead you i was going to say
you could see them uh
you could see them go underground and
move to
the weather underground uh bombing and
assassination model
uh i don't believe that will be the case
just because they found out it wasn't
effective last time
yeah uh but it's you know because you
remember you had the the spasms of
street violence
uh in um in these you know
at the democratic convention uh and
and when that didn't work then they went
underground right uh and they started
their bombings and the armored car
robberies and the kidnappings and all
this crazy stuff
so it's possible they could go in that
direction i don't know yeah and since
we've seen them
antifa as an idea and an organization
and a movement
action-oriented idea which makes them a
thing
we've seen them go underground when they
need to we've seen them slither from one
environment to the next we've seen them
mutate
and evolve and so it's likely that they
will never go away but it is there is a
chance if trump is elected that there
will be
a flash and then perhaps a pause if
biden is elected my belief is that
they're going to do everything they can
to continue to drag them to the left
continue to impact the agenda and the
political discourse
and god forbid that there's going to be
some sort of truth and reconciliation
program that takes place
uh that's code word for you know come
after all of us and and
and end us and cancel us and kill us uh
in
a in a biden administration where they
think to themselves
okay this trump thing was a was a
one-time event
it's an anomaly it's an aberration and
we have to just
extinguish it right now and we have to
put these people away
and make sure this is my big fear that
biden gets elected and then this
attitude we've got to make sure this
will never happen again and this is
trump
that this trump thing will never happen
again and so they're gonna
they're gonna be very active in making
sure to extinguish
any remnants of the trump administration
trump supporters
trumpet trumpism any of the policies or
ideas that he's tried to implement so
it's going to be crazy time coming up
man that's really all there is to it
kyle thank you
oh yeah you want to say one more thing
well i was just going to say uh
you know people should remember that the
irs targeting of conservatives
uh happened under the obama
administration uh that the ferguson
riots
happened in the obama administration so
the idea that
these sorts of things go away or that
people that spoke out or ran
organizations or
you know as trump leaves government and
seeks to set up you know some kind of
non-profit to continue to move forward
with his ideas that these things can't
be targeted uh
i think is wrong i mean they i think
they will be targeted so
uh and and again as i said ferguson
happened under
uh obama so don't think that we won't
see
more disorder more riots more
insurrection
uh just because we have a democratic
administration i don't think that's the
case
definitely not going to be the case
whatsoever uh
in fact they may be emboldened and so
the the post the post-2020 election
period
is one that's fraught with um
uncertainty
and uh it does look to be sort of
chaotic
moving forward so kyle um let's touch
base again
in a couple of months and see where
things are thank you so much for giving
us your time and energy today your
expertise is invaluable on this matter
i hope that congress and our national
security apparatus listen to you more
and they pay closer attention to what's
going on you're doing great work i
really appreciate your time and energy
stick around with me for a second after
we sign off but uh kyle scheidler ladies
and gentlemen
uh please find him at the center for
security policy
my name is jack murphy find me on jack
murphy live jackmurphylive.com get the
book democrat to deplorable
and if you want to be part of an info
militia if you want to be a part of a
group of men
that make it their goal to understand
the world today and preserve
our values of masculinity sovereignty
and brotherhood come down check out the
liminal order at liminal hyphen order
dot com thank you everybody
we'll be back soon upcoming guests
include john robb alum bakari
and uh this gentleman who wrote a book
called war for eternity about
dugan bannon and olavo it's gonna be
fascinating
thanks everybody for listening catch you
later on jack murphy live thank you